Contact

kla.stafford@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kaylastafford-22788313a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing
Patient Advocacy
Customer Satisfaction

Certifications

Injectables Training Program
Pediatric Advanced Life Support
(PALS)
Basic Life Support (BLS)
NRP

Kayla Stafford

Registered Nurse

Atlanta

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Cares for the tiniest humans. Skilled in Patient Care, Advocacy, Safety and Satisfaction. Strong healthcare services professional with a BSN focused in Nursing from University of Indianapolis.

Experience

WellStar Health System
Registered Nurse - NICU
December 2017 - Present (2 years 9 months)
Greater Atlanta Area

Level III NICU - Floating between all Wellstar Health System NICUs to accommodate staffing/census needs. Providing direct patient care to neonates. Attending high risk deliveries and assisting with newborn admissions.

Emory Healthcare
Registered Nurse - NICU
November 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months)
Atlanta, Georgia

Level III NICU

Agency

Travel Registered Nurse - NICU June 2017 - November 2017 (6 months)

Atlanta, Georgia

Level III NICU - Piedmont Atlanta Hospital & Grady Memorial Hospital.

Memorial Hermann Health System Registered Nurse - NICU May 2016 - June 2017 (1 year 2 months) Houston, Texas

Level IV NICU

Riley Children's Hospital @ Methodist/IU Health Registered Nurse - NICU June 2015 - May 2016 (1 year) Indianapolis, Indiana

Level III NICU

RCI | Vacation Exchange Travel Agent / Supervisor November 2006 - October 2013 (7 years) Carmel, Indiana

Education

University of Indianapolis
BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse